{
    "subject": "resource/Mark_Miloscia",
    "predicate": "ontology/almaMater",
    "object": "resource/Chapman_University",
    "human_readable": "Mark Miloscia attended Chapman University.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9747350811958313,
            "question": "Is Chapman University a place Mark Miloscia has studied at?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9455844759941101,
            "question": "Name a university that Mark Miloscia attended."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.909179151058197,
            "question": "Where did Mark Miloscia attend university?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8633298873901367,
            "question": "What is the name of the university Mark Miloscia attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8015272617340088,
            "question": "What educational institution did Mark Miloscia attend?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7453474402427673,
            "question": "At what university did Mark Miloscia study?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.735205352306366,
            "question": "What is the name of the university Mark Miloscia went to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7217311859130859,
            "question": "Did Mark Miloscia go to college?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7214543223381042,
            "question": "Which university is connected to Mark Miloscia?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3815460503101349,
            "question": "What institution of higher learning was Mark Miloscia associated with?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Mark Miloscia attended Chapman University.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6483_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which university is connected to Mark Miloscia?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6483_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Mark Miloscia go to college?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6483_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the university Mark Miloscia went to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6483_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6483_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6483_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6483_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6483_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6483_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6483_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6483_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6483_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6483_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6483_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Mark Miloscia attended Chapman University. The document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_6483/re-ranker-msmarco/37.txt states: \"Miloscia holds an MBA from the University of North Dakota and an M.A.  from Chapman University.\""
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that \"Miloscia holds an M.A. from Chapman University,\" which confirms that Mark Miloscia attended Chapman University."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}